Guide to the Spy Hop Productions independent film collection 2000-2009
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Refugee documentary projects raw rootage, 2003; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 110)
  - Raw footage for Spy Hop documentary "From Somalia to Salt Lake" also possibly used for "Dream Come True?" involving teen refugees living in Salt Lake, 2003 (Video 1)
    Dream Come True? - Documentary. Teens attending Highland High School's magnet program for English as a Second Language (ESL), discuss their experiences as students at Highland High School, give their own definitions of the word "refugee," and what the word means to them. The refugee students (particularly those from Somalia) then ask students and teachers what they believe refugees are and what they think about the number of refugee students at Highland High School. Refugee students also discuss peer pressure, acceptance from local students, and the friends and family they left behind when they came to the United States. The refugee students are then followed home to show their homes and to describe their culture, religion, and how those things have been affected since they came to America (see item 7).
- Ten years, ten audio tracks, ten short films: a decade of empowering youth through multimedia (video), 1999-2009; DVD (Disc 111)
  - "Jules", 1999 (Video 1)
  - "The Hour Glass Project", 2000 (Video 2)
  - "Up:Right", 2001 (Video 3)
  - "Space Cats", 2002 (Video 4)
  - Media literacy public service announcement series, 2003 (Video 5)
  - "No News is Good News", 2004 (Video 6)
  - "Mother Superior", 2005 (Video 7)
  - "Out of Mind", 2006 (Video 8)
  - "Jerry", 2007 (Video 9)
  - "Social Obscurity", 2008 (Video 10)
- Ten years, ten audio tracks, ten short films: a decade of empowering youth through multimedia, 1999-2009; compact disc (Disc 112)
  - Audio tracks, 1999-2009 (Video 1)
    "I See the Beauty" - Heather Smith
    "Island Girl" - Paki Vahe
    "My Home" - Marcus Alvarez
    "Path to Faith" - Rising Roots
    "Drive-By" - Victor Sida
    "Polar Bears" - Steven Schmit, Connery Johnson and Angela Warnick
    "The Infection" - Ryan Cron
    "Dirty Socks" - Erin Haley
    "Company" - Wren Kennedy
    "Grandmother" - Shannalee Otanez